Guide to the Frank Espada photographs and papers, 1946-2010 and undated, bulk 1964-2000 RL.00367
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1979-1991 and undated; 2 boxes
  - Oral History Interviews, 1979-1983
    - Soto, Tony - La Casa, Hartford, CT, 1980-01-31 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0023, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001023)
    - Dawes, Nelson - Hartford, CT, 1980-01-31 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0024, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001024)
    - Torres, Calixtro - CAMINEMOS, Hartford, CT, 1980-02-01 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0025, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001025)
    - Gonzalez, Antonio - City Hall, Hartford, CT, 1980-02-01 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0026, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001026)
    - Rodriguez, Luis - IBA, Boston, MA, 1980-02-19 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0027, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001027)
    - Arana, Nick - CONCILIO, Boston, MA, 1980-02-19 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0028, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001028)
    - Rodriguez, Gladys - ALIANZA, Boston, MA, 1980-02-20 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0029, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001029)
    - Perez, Ana Hernandez - ALIANZA, Boston, MA, 1980-02-21 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0029, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001029)
    - Ortiz, Raquel - LA PLAZA/WGBH, Boston, MA, 1980-02-21 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0030, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001030)
    - Stewart, Inez - P. R. COMMONWEALTH, Boston, MA, 1980-02-21 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0030, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001030)
    - Valdiris, Gil; Rivera, Gregorio; Delgado, Jose - Areyto, Boston, MA, 1980-02-21 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0031, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001031)
    - Alers, Oscar - P.R. MIGRATION CONSORTIUM, New York, NY, 1980-03-07 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0032, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001032)
    - Diaz Jr., Manny - New York, NY, 1980-03-20 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0033, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001033)
    - Agueros, Jack - Museo del Bario, New York, NY, 1980-03-20 (Box 33, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0034, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001034)
    - Roriguez, Robert - Councilman, New York, NY, 1980-03-21 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0035, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001035)
    - Antonetti, Evelina - UNITED BRONX PARENTS, Bronx, NY, 1980-03-21 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0036, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001036)
    - Dominguez, Angel - Farmworkers Corperation/CATA, Vineland, NJ, 1980-04-01 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0037, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001037)
    - Rodriguez, Tommy - Vineland, NJ, 1980-04-01 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0038, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001038)
    - Roman, Alfonso - CONGRESO de NJ, Trenton, NJ, 1980-04-02 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0038, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001038)
    - Roman, Alfonso - CONGRESO de NJ, Trenton, NJ, 1980-04-02 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0039, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001039)
    - Torres, Miguel - Downtown Urban Housing Development, Jersey City, NJ, 1980-04-03 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0040, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001040)
    - Vasquez, Jaime - Newark, NJ, 1980-04-04 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0040, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001040)
    - Rosario, Jose - FOCUS, Newark, NJ, 1980-04-03 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0041, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001041)
    - Rivera, Eliu - PACO, Jersey City, NJ, 1980-04-03 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0041, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001041)
    - Colon, Miriam - P.R. TRAVELLING THEATRE. New York, NY, 1981 January (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0042, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001042)
    - Acuna, Jose - Manhattan Valley Development, New York, NY, 1981-01 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0043, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001043)
    - Colon, Johnny - East Harlem Music School, New York, NY, 1981-01 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0044, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001044)
    - Boricua College Students - Boricua College, New York, NY, 1981-01 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0045, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001045)
    - Torres, Robert - Las Piedras, PR, 1981-02-26 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0046, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001046)
    - Medina, Anthony; Encaracion, Orlando; Falcon, Jorge - Las Piedras, PR, 1981-02-26 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0046, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001046)
    - Four Students - EDUCACION A ESTUDIANTES MIGRATORIOS, Ramon Power High School, Las Piedras, PR, 1981-02-26 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0047, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001047)
    - Figueroa, Jose - Las Piedras, PR, 1981-02-26 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0048, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001048)
    - Santos, Rosa and family - Urb. Country Club, Rio Piedras, PR, 1981-02-28 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0049, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001049)
    - Reyes, Avelino and Wilma - Rio Piedras, PR, 1981-03-04 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0050, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001050)
    - Rios, Peter and family - Santurce, PR, 1981-03-05 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0051, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001051)
    - Hernandez, Maria and Juan - Las Piedras, PR, 1981-03-07 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0052, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001052)
    - Aponte, Ismael and Ana - Las Piedras, PR, 1981-03-07 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0052, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001052)
    - Castro, Antonia - Juncos, PR, 1981-03-07 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0053, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001053)
    - Encarnacion, Janet and Orlando - Juncos, PR, 1981-03-07 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0053, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001053)
    - Arroyo, Rudy; Pangit, Walter; Custodio, Albert - Shinka House Residents, Oahu, HI, 1981-03-30 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0054, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001054)
    - Morales, Rodney and Ann - Honolulu, HI, 1981-04-02 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0055, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001055)
    - Vegas, John - Honolulu, HI, 1981-04-03 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0056, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001056)
    - Rios, Tana and Ralph - Honolulu, HI, 1981-04-03 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0057, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001057)
    - Young people in Hawaii - Honolulu, HI, 1981-04-04 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0058, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001058)
    - Matias, Johnny and Julia - Honolulu, HI, 1981-04-05 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0059, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001059)
    - Velez, Joseph - Kapala, HI, 1981-04-06 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0060, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001060)
    - Riveria, Confessor and Diaz, Tony - Kona, HI, 1981-04-06 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0061, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001061)
    - Riveria, Confessor and Diaz, Tony - Kona, HI, 1981-04-06 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0062, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001062)
    - At Confessor Riveira's house - Kona, HI, 1981-04-08 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0063, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001063)
    - Diaz, Tony and Emily; Rivera, Ethel; Espada, Marilyn and Frank - Confessor's Riveira's house, Kona, HI, 1981-04-08 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0064, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001064)
    - Caravalho, Santos - Hilo, HI, 1981-04-10 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0065, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001065)
    - Rodriguez, Carmen - New York, NY, 1980-03-18 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0066, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001066)
    - Rodriguez, Jamie and Diaz, Rafael - Las Piedras, PR, 1981-02-27 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0067, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001067)
    - Collazo, Tony - Los Angeles, CA, 1981-04-19 (Box 53, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0068, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001068)
    - Santiago, David - Los Angeles, CA, 1981-04-19 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0069, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001069)
    - Batis, Eddie - Los Angeles, CA, 1981-04-20 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0070, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001070)
    - Aguizoni, Sonny - Los Angeles, CA, 1981-04-22 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0071, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001071)
    - Cheveres, Tommy - San Leandro, CA, 1981-04-28 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0072, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001072)
    - Calderon De Romero, Lila San Leandro, CA, 1981-04-29 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0073, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001073)
    - Huertas, Edelmiro - San Francisco, CA, 1981-05-01 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0074, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001074)
    - Rivera, Eddie - San Francisco, CA, 1981-05-01 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0075, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001075)
    - Rodriguez, Moises - Hayward, CA, 1981-05-02 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0076, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001076)
    - Young People in Harrisburg - CENTRO DE VIDA, Harrisburg, PA, 1981-05-27 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0077, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001077)
    - Jimenez, Angel Luis - Reading, PA, 1981-05-28 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0078, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001078)
    - ESL Program - Advanced - Harrisburg, PA, 1981-05 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0079, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001079)
    - ESL Program - Basic - Harrisburg, PA, 1981-05 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0079, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001079)
    - Molina, Manuel and Sandra - Kennet Square, PA, 1981-05-29 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0080, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001080)
    - Quinones, Margarita - LA COMUNIDAD HISPANA, Kennet Square, PA, 1981-05-29 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0081, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001081)
    - Martinez, Marcelino and Lopez, Ped; Montalvo, Elsie - Mushroom workers, Kennett Square, PA, 1981-06 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0082, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001082)
    - Montalvo, Elsie - Bilingual teacher, Kennett Square, PA, 1981-06 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0082, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001082)
    - Molina, Ricardo - Welding trainee, Lancaster, PA, 1981-06-02 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0083, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001083)
    - Exia, Edgardo and Carrion, Clara - Welding instructor and welding trainee, Lancaster, PA, 1981-06-02 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0083, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001083)
    - Pereira, Angel Luis - Lancaster, PA, 1981-06-02 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0084, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001084)
    - Valentin, Adela - Lancaster, PA, 1981-06-02 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0084, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001084)
    - Yiengst, Raquel - Bilingual program director, Reading, PA, 1981-06-04 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0085, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001085)
    - Echevarria, Angie - Los Angeles, CA, 1981-04-19 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0086, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001086)
    - Kerns, Margarita Morales - ESL Program, Harrisburg, PA, 1981-05 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0087, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001087)
    - Perales, Cesar - New York, NY, 1981-06 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0088, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001088)
    - Moises, Doris - PROMESA, South Bronx, NY, 1983-11-11 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0089, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001089)
    - Bentencourt, Ismael - The Plant, South Bronx, NY, 1981-06 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0090, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001090)
    - Bentencourt, Ismael - LaGallera, South Bronx, NY, 1981-06 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0091, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001091)
    - Acuna, Jose and the Pacheco-Baez Family - Manhattan Valley, NY, 1981-06 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0092, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001092)
    - Acuna, Jose - New York, NY, 1981-06 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0092, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001092)
    - Vazquez, Willie - Washington, DC, 1981-06 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0093, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001093)
    - Caro, Eugenio - Hartford, CT, 1981-10-19 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0094, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001094)
    - Caro, Eugenio - Hartford, CT, 1981-10-19 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0095, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001095)
    - Laboy, Robert - Hartford, CT, 1981-10-21 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0096, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001096)
    - Fernandez, Max -Hartford, CT, 1981-10-21 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0097, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001097)
    - Sanchez, Maria -Hartford, CT, 1981-10-21 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0098, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001098)
    - Serrano, Maria - Hartford, CT, 1981-10-21 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0098, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001098)
    - Negron, Edna - Hartford, CT, 1981-10-22 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0099, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001099)
    - Soto, Mildred Torres -Hartford, CT, 1981-10-22 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0100, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001100)
    - Soto, Mildred Torres -Hartford, CT, 1981-10-22 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0101, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001101)
    - Housing Meeting - Hartford, CT, 1981-10-22 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0101, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001101)
    - Borrero, Maria - Hispanic Health Council, Hartford, CT, 1981-10-22 (Box 54, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0102, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001102)
    - Soto, Tony - Hartford, CT, 1981-10-23 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0103, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001103)
    - Soto, Tony Hartford, CT, 1981-10-22 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0104, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001104)
    - Saenz, Alberto Garcia - Bronx, NY, 1981-11 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0105, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001105)
    - Gonzalez, Juan - Philadelphia, PA, 1982-02-11 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0106, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001106)
    - Gonzalez, Juan - Philadelphia, PA, 1982-02-11 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0107, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001107)
    - Betances, Samuel - Chicago, IL, 1982-02-14 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0108, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001108)
    - Betances, Samuel - Chicago, IL, 1982-02-14 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0109, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001109)
    - Dominguez, Angel - CATA, Glassboro, NJ, 1982-05 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0110, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001110)
    - Gonzales, Petra - Penn's Grove, NJ, 1982-05 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0111, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001111)
    - Ortiz, Juan - Vineland, NJ, 1982-05 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0112, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001112)
    - Quinones, Pedro Caravallo - Vineland, NJ, 1982-05 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0113, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001113)
    - Ortiz, Juan -Vineland, NJ, 1982-05 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0113, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001113)
    - CATA Meeting - Vineland, NJ, 1982-05-27 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0114, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001114)
    - Durio, Lenny - Savage Nomads, Hartford, CT, 1982-06 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0115, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001115)
    - At Cookie's House - Hartford, CT, 1982-06 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0116, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001116)
    - De Jesus, Marta - Centro San Lazaro, Hartford, CT, 1982-06 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0117, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001117)
    - Centro San Lazaro - Hartford, CT, 1982-06 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0117, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001117)
    - Jimenez, Marta - Chicago, IL, 1982-08-26 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0118, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001118)
    - Jimenez, Tommy - Chicago, IL, 1982-08-26 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0119, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001119)
    - Jimenez, Angel - Chicago, IL, 1982-08-26 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0119, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001119)
    - Gonzalez, Richard - Chicago, IL, 1982-08 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0120, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001120)
    - Collazo, Luis and Genoveva - Chicago, IL, 1982-08 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0121, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001121)
    - Collazo, Willie - Chicago, IL, 1982-08 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0121, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001121)
    - Aulet, Carlos - Chicago, IL, 1982-08 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0122, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001122)
    - Caraballo, George and Carmen - Maui, HI, 1983-02 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0123, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001123)
    - Vega, Solomon and Espinoza, Maria - Aiea, Oahu, HI, 1983-02-04 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0124, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001124)
    - Vega, Solomon - Aiea, Oahu, HI, 1983-02-04 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0124, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001124)
    - Baez, Tony - Milwaukee, WI, 1983-05 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0125, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001125)
    - Baez, Tony - Milwaukee, WI, 1983-05 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0126, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001126)
    - Baez, Luis and Pablo - Milwaukee, WI, 1983-06-05 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0127, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001127)
    - Cruz, Pedro - Juana Diaz Bar, Milwaukee, WI, 1983-05 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0128, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001128)
    - Pabon, Cesar - Milwaukee, WI, 1983-05 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0128, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001128)
    - Acosta, Israel - Milwaukee, WI, 1983-06-04 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0129, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001129)
    - Gonzalez, Tony - Milwaukee, WI, 1983-06-04 (Box 55, Audio-cassette RL00367-CS-0129, Digital-materials Duke Digital Repository Item ID: espau001129)